"Indians r poor but India is not a poor country. Says one of the swiss bank directors. He says that "" &lt;#&gt;  lac crore"" of Indian money is deposited in swiss banks which can be used for 'taxless' budget for  &lt;#&gt;  yrs. Can give  &lt;#&gt;  crore jobs to all Indians. From any village to Delhi 4 lane roads. Forever free power suply to more than  &lt;#&gt;  social projects. Every citizen can get monthly  &lt;#&gt; /- for  &lt;#&gt;  yrs. No need of World Bank &amp; IMF loan. Think how our money is blocked by rich politicians. We have full rights against corrupt politicians. Itna forward karo ki pura INDIA padhe.g.m."""
